Uh, huh, uh, huh (yeah, Rihanna)
Uh, huh, uh, huh (good girl gone bad)
Uh, huh, uh, huh (take three, action)
Uh, huh, uh, huh (Hov)

No clouds in my stones
Let it rain, I hydroplane in the bank (eh, eh, eh)
Coming down with the Dow Jones
When the clouds come, we gone, we Roc-A-Fella (eh, eh, eh, eh)
We fly higher than weather, in G5's or better
You know me
In anticipation for precipitation stack chips for the rainy day (eh, eh, eh)
Jay, Rain Man is back (eh, eh, eh)
With little Ms. Sunshine, Rihanna, where you at?

You have my heart
And we'll never be worlds apart
May be in magazines
But you'll still be my star
Baby, 'cause in the dark
You can't see shiny cars
And that's when you need me there
With you I'll always share

Because
When the Sun shine, we shine together
Told you I'll be here forever
Said I'll always be your friend
Took an oath, I'mma stick it out to the end
Now that it's raining more than ever
Know that we'll still have each other
You can stand under my umbrella
You can stand under my umbrella

Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh

These fancy things
Will never come in between
You're part of my entity
Here for infinity
When the war has took its part
When the world has dealt its cards
If the hand is hard
Together we'll mend your heart

Because
When the Sun shine, we shine together
Told you I'll be here forever
Said I'll always be your friend
Took an oath, I'mma stick it out to the end
Now that it's raining more than ever
Know that we'll still have each other
You can stand under my umbrella
You can stand under my umbrella

Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh
Under my umbrella
Ella, ella, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh

You can run into my arms
It's okay, don't be alarmed
Come into me
There's no distance in between our love
So go on and let the rain pour
I'll be all you need and more, oh
